这件案子来自于垃圾场
Job came in about an hour ago from sanitation.
没有其他什么了 只有头吗
There was nothing else? Just the head?
法医在路上了
So far. M.E.'s office is on the way.
完全腐烂了
Pretty decomposed.
你为什么不去那里近距离观察一下呢
Why don't you go on up there and have a closer look?
他刚刚说过法医在路上了
He just said M.E.'s on the way.
我去找他们 快去啊
I'll look out for them. Go on.
你考试当警探的时候
When you were taking the test,
从没想过自己要爬到一堆垃圾上
you ever think you'd be climbing up a pile of garbage
看一颗断头吧
to get to a severed head?
没有 我以为我更像
No. Thought I'd be more like
《阿帕奇要塞》里面的保罗·纽曼
Paul Newman in Fort Apache, The Bronx.
都是80年代的罪案类美剧
对我来说是《警花拍档》
It was Cagney & Lacey for me.
你知道我们可以退休
You know we could just retire,
然后去一座热带小岛上破案
and go to a tropical island and solve crimes there.
可以是可以
We could, but you would
但你离开纽约的五个区就活不下去了吧
never survive outside the five boroughs.
也是哈
That's true.
是的 这是曼诺·圣戈亚托
Yeah, it's Mano Sangriento.
黑手标志吗
Black hand?
没 这里只有手指 不过之前是只手
No, just the fingers. But it was a hand.
那是个名片
That's the calling card.
是啊 现在我们要查清楚
Yeah. Now we're gonna have to figure out
这个家伙为什么丢了脑袋
why this guy lost his head.
约瑟·科特斯 30岁 来自日落公园
Jose Cortez, 30, from Sunset Park.
警察发现他身上有半盎司可卡因
Cops found him in possession of a half-ounce of cocaine.
属于三级携带犯罪
Criminal possession in the third degree.
但科特斯之前没有犯罪记录 所以他
But Cortez has no priors, so he's eligible
可以进行司法转移
for judicial diversion.
所以他会进行药物治疗而非坐牢
So he'll get drug treatment instead of jail time.
而且施耐德曼帮他辩护 所以毫无疑问她会建议进行康复
And Schneiderman is on deck, so no doubt she'll recommend rehab.
你再三确认过他在纽约之外的地方
You run a triple I check to make sure he doesn't have
没有犯罪记录吗
a record outside of New York?
他的记录很干净 法律援助会要求自签担保释放
His record's clean. Legal aid's gonna ask for R.O.R.
指当事人无需缴纳保释金 以自己的名誉作为担保
向法官作出一定的承诺后有条件的释放
你想做什么
What do you want to do?
我要500块保释金
I'll ask for 500 bail.
她无论如何都会让他自签担保释放
She'll R.O.R. Him anyway.
就那么着呗
And so it goes.
好吧 你看起来胸有成竹
All right, well, you seem to have everything under control.
你需要我做什么吗
You need anything from me?
涨工资
A raise.
排队等
Get in line.
要来点早餐吗
You want some breakfast?
甘蓝和蛋白粉吗 还是不了
Kale and protein powder? I think I'll pass.
如果你能脱下睡袍 我会让你心想事成
If you show me what's under that robe, I'll make you
好吧 既然如此
- whatever you want. - Well, in that case,
你得做一些味道惊艳的薄饼
you're gonna have to produce some pretty killer pancakes.
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
希望我没有诉讼案件
Wish I didn't have court.
嗯 这比堵在泽西的路上要好得多
Mm. It's better than being stuck in Jersey traffic.
不 我的意思是 我希望能与你同行一起去
No, I mean, I wish I could come with you.
没什么大不了的
It's no biggie.
告诉你妈妈我们订婚是件大事
Telling your mom that we're engaged is a biggie.
- 嗯 - 而且 我还没见过她呢
- Mm... - Plus, I haven't even met her yet.
是的 就保持那样吧
Exactly. Let's keep it that way.
什么意思
What does that mean?
我妈妈吓跑了
My mother has scared off
每一位介绍给她的男朋友
every boyfriend I've ever introduced her to.
我不是每一位男朋友
I'm not every boyfriend.
好吧 你见到她的时候亲自体会吧
Well, then you'll see for yourself when you meet her.
婚礼的时候
At the wedding.
太荒唐了
Ridiculous.
埃迪 大新闻 我的开庭日期推迟到明天了
Eddie, great news. My court date got pushed to tomorrow.
哦
Oh.
- 我可以和你一起了 - 等等 什么
- I can come with you. - Wait, what?
嗯 我会跟你一起去
Yeah, I'll just take the day and come with you.
不行 绝对不行
No, definitely not.
隐身 绝对是隐形能力
Invisibility. Definitely invisibility.
不 老兄 蜘蛛感应
No, man. Spidey-sense.
然后 有事情发生的时候你会收到警告
Then, you get fair warning when something's gonna go down.
透视眼怎么样
How about X-ray vision?
呃 不 有一些我不想看到的事情
Ugh, no. There are things I don't want to see.
我一直希望我有真言索套
I've always had a thing for the Lasso of Truth.
我们当上警探的时候肯定有用
Come in handy when we make detective.
嘿 你们为什么老是称量大脑
Hey, why do you guys always weigh the brain?
看看它们多重
To see how much they weigh.
实际上 是为了发现异常
Actually, it's to look for abnormalities.
这个
This one is
有三磅重的记忆 情绪
three pounds of memories, emotions
和860亿神经细胞
and 86 billion nerve cells.
嗯
Hmm.
我一直好奇控制情绪的部分
I've always wondered about the part that controls your emotion.
哦 杏仁体
Oh, the amygdala.
有时有点希望能移掉它
Kind of wish I could have it removed sometimes.
是啊 那时你就会成为连环杀手
Yeah, but then you'd be a serial killer.
呃 你能告诉我们你发现了什么
Uh, what can you tell us about
关于垃圾堆里的那颗脑袋
the head you found at the garbage dump?
我在等DNA结果 但死亡时间和造成的伤害
I'm waiting on DNA, but the time of death and the injuries
和几周前你们带给我的无头尸体
are consistent with that headless corpse
是一致的
you guys brought me a few weeks ago.
你是说路易斯·德尔加多的头
You mean the one belonging to Luis Delgado?
那具身体不是路易斯·德尔加多
That body wasn't Luis Delgado.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
那具身体和你们今天早上在垃圾堆找到的头
That body and the head that you pulled out from the garbage
属于同一个人
this morning appear to belong to the same person.
不可能 我们在沙滩上找到的身体
No, the body we found on the beach
穿着路易斯·德尔加多的衣服
with Luis Delgado's clothes on and Luis Delgado's tattoos
纹着路易斯·德尔加多的纹身
belong to Luis Delgado.
相信我吧
Trust me.
我已经和墨西哥给的牙医记录做过确认了
I had to get dental records from Mexico to confirm.
太好了 也就是说
Great. Then the son of a bitch
烧了我家房子的那个王八羔子还活着
who burned down my house is still alive.
怎么回事
What is it?
两名警官在证人家外的巡逻车内
Two officers sitting on a witness's house
身中数弹
were shot multiple times inside their patrol car.
枪枪致命
Both critical.
- 有人生还吗 - 消息源源不断
- Anyone likely? - Information's still coming in.
他们在Saint Irene医院
They're at Saint Irene's.
枪手的消息呢
And the shooter?
还没有
No word yet.
弗兰克 其中的一名警官
Frank, one of the officers
是艾比盖尔的丈夫
is Abigail's husband.
翻译 冰熊
蓝
白色
的
甜
栗
子
翻译 司令原
北
极熊
小
白
校对
蓝
白色
的
甜
栗
子
总校 蓝白色的甜栗子
特
效
Shey
l
a
压制 蓝白色的甜栗子
总监
蓝
白
色
的
甜
栗
子
警
察
世
家
第九季     第七集
不择手段
By Hook or by Crook
本字幕由蓝血字幕组
译制
仅供交流学习 严禁用于任何商业盈利行为
嘿
Hey.
两名警察在巡逻车里中枪
Two cops were shot in their patrol car.
我听说了 他们情况如何
I heard. Any word on their condition?
蓝血字幕组
还在等 但是艾琳
Still waiting. But Erin,
他们刚刚找到了枪手
they just picked up the shooter.
是约瑟·科尔特斯
It's Jose Cortez.
我们今天早上放走的那个人吗
The guy we released this morning?
蓝血字幕组
他从提审法院直接回到公寓
He went straight from arraignment court
拿了一把0.45口径的枪开火
to his apartment, he picked up a .45
他有过谋杀与威胁他人的记录
and he opened fire. He's got a record for murder and assault.
不可能 他的犯罪记录是空的
No. His rap sheet came up empty.
在我们的系统是空的
It came up empty in our system
是因为他之前的犯罪记录在墨西哥
because his priors were in Mexico.
安东尼 这是我的错
Anthony, this is my fault.
不
No.
你的助理检察官严格遵循了
Your A.D.A. Followed the bail recommendations
推荐保释制度
to the letter.
去跟躺在医院里的
Tell that to the two cops
那两名警察说去
laying in the hospital.
戴维斯警官已经做完手术
Officer Davis is out of surgery.
他正在恢复中
He's in recovery.
一颗子弹打到了布莱恩的脖子上
Brian took a bullet to his neck,
切断了他的颈静脉
which severed his jugular.
我给你看过布莱恩的证件照片吗
Did I ever show you Brian's department photo?
这不太合理 但他还是笑了
You're not supposed to, but... he smiled.
故意地
On purpose.
他说你每次看到警察
He said every time you see a cop shot
在报纸的头版
on the front page of the paper,
通常都是证件照片 看起来很严肃
it's always the official photo and they look so serious.
他还想如果他笑的话 那是...
He figured if he smiled, it was...
一种他不会发生坏事情的保证
some sort of guarantee that nothing bad would happen to him.
他可能是对的
He might be right.
我答应他 只要他能好转 我做什么都心甘情愿
I've promised him all kinds of things if he gets better.
布莱恩
Brian,
我是雷根局长
it's Commissioner Reagan.
不惜一切 艾比盖尔
Whatever it takes, Abigail.
我告诉你
I'm telling you,
德尔加多让这个家伙乔装打扮的看起来像自己
Delgado had this guy made up to look like him,
甚至到纹身
even down to the tattoo,
所以他才能骗过我们
so he could pull one over on us.
曼诺·圣戈亚托现在已经遍及长岛和曼哈顿
Mano Sangriento is all over Long Island and Manhattan now.
- 他们都用黑手 - 他耍了我们
- They all use the black hand. - He played us.
我查过所有的轮船和飞机乘客名单
I've checked every ship and airline passenger list.
我认为他还没离开镇子
I don't think he left town.
嘿 好几周了 好吗
Look, it's been weeks, okay?
他现在可能在任何地方 包括墨西哥
He could be anywhere by now, including Mexico.
联系缉毒局吧
Just speak to the DEA.
看看他们能否提供一些线索
See if they'll give you anything they got on him.
我再去核查一下我妹给我的他手机的搜查令
I'll check the warrant my sister gave me on his cell phone
看看有什么蛛丝马迹
and see if that turns anything up.
我觉得应该让别人去找德尔加多了
I think someone else should find Delgado.
你跟他之间有点
It's way too personal
私人恩怨了
between you and him. I'm not gonna go
如果你那样以为的话 我不会做越轨的事的 明白吧
off the rails, if that's what you're thinking, okay?
我保证
I promise.
你已经那样做了
You already did.
你真的想让我们俩成为众矢之的了吗
Do you really want to put us in the crosshairs?
你听着 不管付出什么代价
Look, I'm gonna get that son of a bitch,
我就是要抓住那个狗娘养的
no matter what it takes.
你不想加入一起做的话
You don't want to be a part of that,
那我建议你可以选择离开
then I suggest you walk away on this one.
你真的想让我离开吗
You really want me to walk away?
妈妈
Mom.
嗨
Hi.
- 嗯额  - 这是杰米
- Hmm. - This is Jamie.
嗨
Hi.
你之前没告诉我你要带人过来了
You didn't tell me you were bringing someone.
- 我知道 抱歉啦  - 杰米·雷根 很高兴见到你
- I know. I'm sorry. - Jamie Reagan. Nice to meet you.
最近还好吧
How do you do?
还不错
Very well.
不客气
You're welcome.
额 我能用一下这把椅子吧
Um... Can I steal this?
好的 没问题
Yes, no problem.
那
So...
你们是在约会吗
are you dating?
这算是新男朋友吗
Is this, like, a new boyfriend?
唔 他是我未婚夫
Uh, he-he's my fiancé.
未婚夫
Fiancé?
这是我第一次见你吧
And this is the first time I'm meeting you?
噢噢 我们没有正儿八经地约会过
Well, we didn't really date date.
你们没有约会吗
You didn't date?
他的意思是我们俩已经相识
What he means is we've known each other
很久了
for a long time.
我们在工作中是同伴
We were partners on the job.
那你是一名警察
So you're a cop.
他是一位警长
He's a sergeant.
哈佛毕业的
He went to Harvard.
25万美元的学费
A quarter of a million dollars in tuition
你却决定当个警察
and you decided to be a cop.
好吧 我们家里人都在执法部门
Well, my whole family's in law enforcement,
所以我想可能骨子里就想从警吧
so I guess it was in the blood.
骨子里没有想做医生或者律师 是有点糟糕了
It's too bad doctor or lawyer wasn't in the blood.
如果做医生或律师的话
Then you two could
你们就能过得更滋润了
actually afford a nice lifestyle.
我们很喜欢我们现在的生活方式 妈妈
We love our lifestyle, Mom.
你有房子吗
Do you own a house?
我有一套公寓
I have an apartment.
埃迪喜欢待在市里
Eddie likes being in the city.
- "埃迪" - 没人叫我"小迪" 妈妈
- "Eddie"? - No one calls me Edit, Mom.
我是没叫 但你老爸那样叫你
I do. Your father does.
好吧 我喜欢艾迪这个名字
Well, I like Eddie.
那 你用男孩子的名字 而他用女孩子的名字
So, you use a boy's name and he uses a girl's name.
老妈
Mom.
我只是说说
I'm just saying.
好吧 我的全名叫詹姆森
That's okay. My real name's Jameson.
听起来像威士忌一样
Like the whiskey.
是的 是像威士忌
Yeah, like the whiskey.
[一种伏特加酒的商标名]
你爸妈不喜欢司木露倒还不错
It's a good thing your parents didn't like to drink Smirnoff.
- 妈妈 - 怎么了
- Mom. - What?
那 雷根 是不是跟那个谁有点关系了...
So, Reagan, is that, is that any relation to...
是的 警察局长 那是我爸
The police commissioner, yes, he's my dad.
怎么了
What?
小迪 你肯定是在开玩笑吧
You must see the humor in this, Edit.
你爸爸在坐牢
Your father's in jail,
而你现在要跟警察局长的儿子结婚
and you're marrying the police commissioner's son.
那在你们结婚招待朋友时候 肯定会有很多很有趣的对话
That's going to make for some very interesting conversation
你不觉得吗
at the wedding reception, don't you think?
看样子戴维斯的手受到了永久性神经损伤
Looks like Davis has permanent nerve damage to his hand.
受伤的是惯用枪的手
His shooting hand,
那他以后最好不能再从事在街上的工作了
so he'll be off the street for good.
好吧 也不一定
Well, not necessarily.
那不是现在讨论的事情
Not with the kind of things they can do today.
那布莱恩·贝克呢
And Brian Baker?
老样子
Still the same.
老大 助理检察官雷根来啦
A.D.A. Reagan, boss.
艾琳
Erin.
盖瑞特 希德
Garrett. Sid.
- 艾琳  - 布莱恩怎么样了
- Erin. - How's Brian?
还在昏迷状态
Still unconscious.
现在能做的只有等着
It's a waiting game right now.
那艾比盖尔呢
And Abigail?
艾比盖尔还陪在布莱恩身边
Abigail hasn't left his side.
你上司呢
Where's your boss?
他不来
He's not coming.
好吧
Okay.
我回办公室了 老板
I'll be in my office, boss.
科尔特斯之前是我的案子 我负责监督
Cortez was my case. I supervised it.
那是我的责任
It was my responsibility.
你是怎么想的把他放走了
What were you thinking letting him walk?
他不是被放走了 而是被保释了
He didn't walk. He made bail.
保释金也就500美金 艾琳 那还不就是相当于放他走了
Bail was set at 500 bucks, Erin. Of course he walked.
那些钱对一个毒品贩子来说就不算钱
That's chump change for a drug dealer.
那次逮捕是针对非暴力毒品犯罪的指控
The arrest was for a nonviolent drug charge.
我们不是为了寻求多高的保释金
We are not in the business of asking
而是我们认为某些人是有社会危险性的
for high bail because we think someone might become dangerous.
他在墨西哥有重罪案底 谋杀和故意伤害
He has a felony record in Mexico: murder, assault.
我办公室之前并没有知道这些信息
My office didn't have access to that information.
那地检署
So the D.A.'s office
就急急忙忙地把他放了
is in a rush to hold his hand,
然后他出去就对我们两个警员开枪
and he goes out and shoots two of my cops.
你什么意思 爸爸
What do you want me to say, Dad?
局里的规定就是对非暴力犯罪
The department policy is to ask for little or no bail
只须提供一点甚至不要保释金
for nonviolent crimes.
这个规定过去确实有成效
The policy has had success.
也就那样吧
Not so much.
他在哪里
Where is he?
我不明白你说的谁
I don't know who you're talking about.
在旁边那幅画里你站在他旁边的那个男的
The guy you're standing next to
他在哪儿
in the painting over there. Where is he?
- 唔唔  - 别...
- Uh-uh. - No...
别想了
Don't even think about it.
你非法入侵了
You're trespassing.
强行闯入我家
You broke into my house.
那当你丈夫把我家放火烧了的时候
You mean like your husband trespassed
算不算非法入侵了
when he burned my house down?
妈妈
Mom?
怎么回事了
Is everything okay?
快进里面待着
Go back inside.
- 你手机在哪里  - 在厨房
- Where's your phone? - In the kitchen.
过去拿你的手机
Let's go get it.
你丈夫通过胁迫他人赚了很多钱
Your husband's making a lot of money terrorizing people.
到底是谁在胁迫谁
Who's terrorizing who?
把手机拿起来
Get the phone. Pick it up.
打给你丈夫 快
Call your husband. Come on.
转过身来
Turn around.
别犯傻
Don't do anything crazy.
路易斯
Luis?
嘿 还记得我吧
Hey, remember me?
伊莎贝尔呢 她在旁边
Where's Isabel? She's right here.
孩子也在这里 不过你不用担心 他们是安全的
Kids are here, too. But don't worry, they're safe.
当然 除非我决定烧了你的房子
Unless, of course, I decide to burn your house down
就像你把我的烧了那样
like you burned down mine.
如果你伤害他们
If you harm them,
我发誓我一定会弄死你
I swear I'll kill you.
好啊 那你就快点回来吧
Well, then you better hurry up and get home.
坐下
Sit down.
戴维斯警员右手中了一枪
Officer Davis took a bullet to his right hand,
而且那造成了永久性的神经损伤
which has caused permanent nerve damage.
贝克警员脖子中了一枪
Officer Baker was hit with a bullet in his neck,
击穿了他的颈静脉
which punctured his jugular.
子弹已经被取出来了 但他还没有恢复意识
The bullet was removed, but he has not regained consciousness.
我们会实时更新事件进展
We will have updates as things progress.
有关于枪手的情况吗
What about the shooter?
额 枪手是约瑟·科尔特斯
Uh, the shooter, Jose Cortez,
在枪击发生后很快就被逮捕了
was apprehended shortly after the shooting.
他已经被
He has been charged
以一级谋杀罪起诉了
with attempted murder in the first degree
而且今天下午晚些时候将被传讯
and will be arraigned later this afternoon.
先前的报道称科尔特斯之前刚被拘捕过
Initial reports said Cortez had been arrested before,
但又被取保释放了  - 没错
but released on bail. - That's correct.
他先前因持有毒品被拘捕
He was arrested for drug possession
今天早上交了保释金被释放
and released on bail this morning.
为什么他会被取保释放
Why was he released on bail?
他的犯罪的非暴力性质
The nonviolent nature of his crimes
以及没有刑事犯罪前科
and the lack of prior criminal history.
为什么他一开始就被释放
Why was he released in the first place?
他是曼诺·圣戈亚托的成员
He was a member of Mano Sangriento.
科尔特斯先生没有刑事犯罪历史
Mr. Cortez had no criminal history
和涉枪的案底
or gang affiliation on record.
所以就被作为初犯
It was handled
处理了
as a first-time offense.
你说的案底是什么意思
What do you mean, "On record"?
科尔特斯先生之前在墨西哥有犯罪记录
Mr. Cortez had a prior record in Mexico
而这些在之前的背景审查中没有发现
that did not come up on the initial background check.
鉴于当前的情况 地检署会打算
In light of what happened, is the D.A.'s office
重新考虑更改一下政策吗
going to rethink this policy?
这项政策是为了减少监狱被非暴力犯罪份子
The policy was established to decrease overcrowded prisons
挤满而创立的
filled with nonviolent offenders.
从这方面看 这项政策是成功的
In this regard, the policy is a success.
现在有两名优秀纽约警察局警员躺在医院里
The NYPD has two good officers in the hospital,
其中一个可能残疾
one facing disability,
另外一个还未脱离生命危险
one may not survive.
向一个对我的警员犯下
Asking for minimum bail
重罪的犯人要求最低保释金
for felonies puts my officers
最重要的是
and, more importantly,
他危害了市民安全
our citizens at risk,
因为这种行为会被激励
because these criminals will then be incentivized
将会有更多的人犯更多
to go out and commit more,
更恶劣的罪行
worse crimes.
这就是现在正在发生的事情
And that is exactly what happened today.
就这样
That's all.
谢谢 非常感谢
Thank you. Thank you very much.
我不知道你怎么会想着
I don't know how you actually thought
你可以避免我和你妈见面
you could avoid me meeting your mother.
哦 今天之前我一直做的很好
Oh, I was doing a great job avoiding until today.
埃迪 你已经见过我全家了 他们也并不完美
Eddie, you've met my whole family; they're not perfect.
你有 你知道 你有非常美满的一家
You have... you know, you have a Norman Rockwell family.
你在周日一起去教堂 一起吃饭
You go to church on Sundays, and you eat together on Sundays.
所以不要
Just please don't.
说说罢了 她说的并没有影响到我
Just saying, it doesn't bother me what she says.
她只是说话不经大脑
She just has no filter.
并且她只关心
And she only cares
钱
about money.
埃迪你知道为什么我们每周日都要一起吃饭
Eddie, do you know why we have family dinner every Sunday?
不知道 为啥
No. Why?
因为我的祖母出生在爱尔兰的一个贫困村庄
Because my grandmother grew up poor in a small town in Ireland.
她是十二个孩子里最大的那一个
She was the oldest of 12 kids,
并且吃的从来不够
and there was never enough to eat.
她搬到纽约来挣钱
She moved to New York to make money.
她遇到我的爷爷 然后他们就结婚了
She met my grandpa, and when they got married,
她向自己保证 以后他们一定
she promised herself that they would always
要有足够的食物
have more than enough to eat.
家庭聚餐
Family dinner was
仅仅是她每周完成诺言罢了
just her way of proudly proving that every week.
那顿饭对她如何成长显得很重要
That meal was so important to her because of how she grew up.
我就是说说 一定有一个深层次的原因
I'm just saying, there must be some deep-seated reason
解释为何你妈妈那么看重钱
why your mother is so obsessed about money.
我妈妈选择辱骂我
My mother chooses to insult me
还有我带回家的每一个人
and to insult every person I've ever brought home.
是我 把车停那儿
Yeah. Leave the car there
然后走向车库
and walk to the garage.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
进来吧
Come on in.
这边
Right over there.
把你的手放在
Keep your hands where
- 我能看到的地方 - 我的妻子和儿子呢
- I can see 'em. Where's my wife and my boys?
你为什么要点燃我的房子
Why'd you set my house on fire?
你真的想装作一个无辜的受害者吗
You're really pretending to be an innocent victim?
- 是谁给你下的命令 - 已经没关系了
- Who gave you the order? - Doesn't matter.
你认为你扳倒他 就完了吗
You think if you take him down, it's over?
你们以为你抓到了艾·茶珀
You guys thought you got El Chapo.
抓到一个 还有更多的等着上位
There's 20 guys lining up to be the next El Chapo.
这就是这个组织工作的方式
That's how these organizations work.
我会找到每一个参与过
How this works is that I'm gonna find every son of a bitch
点燃我房子的混蛋
who had a hand in setting my house on fire,
直到他们全都被绳之以法或者更惨
and I'm not gonna stop until every one of them's behind bars,
我才会停手
or worse.
就是这样
That's how it works.
但这不会使你的妻子回来
Won't bring your wife back.
你有两个儿子
You have two sons.
你真的想让他们陷入危险吗
You really want to put them in danger?
贝兹 我抓住德尔加多来
Baez, I got Delgado.
派人到
Request a 10-85
第12贝维尤大道
to 12 Bayview Avenue.
你被捕了 转过身
You're under arrest. Turn around.
手放在背后
Put your hands behind your back.
你犯了一个大错
You made a big mistake.
兄弟 你是一个犯了错的人
You're the one making a mistake, bro.
- 我和你一样 -是吗
- I'm one of you. - Yeah?
怎么说
How's that?
我为缉毒局工作
I'm working for the DEA.
我们有
We have you
你谋杀梅丽莎·桑切斯的证据
for the murder of Melissa Sanchez.
- 不 你没有 - 不 我们有
- No, you don't. - Yes, we do.
你告诉我你杀了她和她未出生的孩子
You told me you killed her and her unborn baby.
我告诉你我不认为她很好
I told you I didn't think she was okay.
事实证明 我是对的
As it turns out, I was right.
她并不好 她死了
She wasn't okay. She was dead.
还有曼尼·桑切斯
And Manny Sanchez.
雷根 你认为你在干什么
Reagan, what do you think you're doing?
你认为你又在干什么
What the hell do you think you're doing?
能出来说吗
Can I talk to you outside?
你在那干什么 更重要的是
What the hell are you doing here? And more importantly,
你怎么会和德尔加多一样的
what the hell are you doing working
人渣一起做事
with a scumbag like Delgado?
- 我们和他达成了协议 - 啊 我知道
- We made a deal with him. - Yeah, I know you did.
你和一个冷血杀手达成了协议
You made a deal with a cold-blooded killer
谁杀害了一个无辜的女子和她未出生的小孩
who murdered an innocent woman and her unborn baby.
德尔加多只是一个打杂的 我们的目标是何塞·罗哈斯
Delgado's a hired hand. We're after José Rojas.
他的上级 拉·阿梅哈 幕后黑手
His boss. La Almeja. The Clam.
- 所以 - 德尔加多只是被他们雇佣了
- Okay. - Delgado is a hired gun.
罗哈斯直接或者间接杀害了数百人
Rojas has murdered or ordered the murder of hundreds.
是吗 我们抓住罗哈斯 我们就扳倒了整个组织
Okay? We get Rojas, we bring down the organization.
很好 让我们去抓他吧
Great, then go get him.
我已经抓住了德尔加多 他是我的了
I already got Delgado. He's mine.
不 你不能插手这件事情
No, you're gonna back off.
门都没有
Go to hell.
你瞧 我知道这对你来说很私人
Look, I get that this has gotten personal for you.
- 不要去那 - 好的 但我们不需要你
- Don't go there. - Okay, but we don't need you
进去到那 当一个刺头 搞砸我们的任务
going in there, being a hothead, blowing our case.
我抓住了德尔加多 他是我的
I arrested Delgado. It's my collar.
你在跟我开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me right now?
我以谋杀逮捕他 知道吗
I got him on murder charges. Okay?
这可比你可能得到的任何毒品起诉更加有料
That trumps any drug charge you could possibly get.
所以你除非你想在法官面前
So unless you want to go before a judge
尝试取得法令让我把他交给
and try to get him to give you a writ for me
联邦的话 请便 除非你那样做
to turn him over to the feds, so be it. You go do that.
在那之前 德尔加多都是我的
But until such time, Delgado's mine.
他将和我呆在这儿
He stays here with me.
嘿
Hey.
什么
What?
或许我们能够合作
Maybe we can work together on this.
额 看来这是唯一的办法
Well, it's the only way
得到我们彼此想要的结果
we're both gonna get what we want.
保佑我们 上帝 这些馈赠
Bless us, O Lord, and these Thy gifts,.
经过耶稣 来自大自然
which we are about to receive from Thy bounty,
慷慨赐予的食物
through Christ our Lord. Amen.
你介意 额 递一下芝士吗
You mind, uh, passing me the mac and cheese?
好的
Sure.
给你
Here you go.
看起来不错
Looks good.
还有丹尼怎么了
And what's the matter with Daniel?
没事
Nothing.
你没有向你的盘子里加东西
Well, you're not piling food onto your plate,
所以一定有事
so it must be something.
额 我有点不想吃了
Well, I kind of lost my appetite
当我知道那个烧掉我房子的人
when I learned that the guy who burned our house down
与缉毒局达成了一份协议
cut a deal with the DEA.
你知道谁烧了我们的房子了吗
You know who burned our house down?
嗯 我们稍后再谈
Yeah. We'll talk about it later.
此时 那家伙像一只鸟一样自由
In the meantime, that guy's walking around free as a bird.
额 你可以一如既往甩锅给地检署
Well, you could always blame the D.A.'s office.
地检署就像是垃圾堆一样任人践踏
It seems to be the common dumping ground around here.
没人在践踏
No one's dumping
地检署
on the D.A.'s office.
你看了
You saw
联合新闻发布会
the joint press conference.
体系漏洞 有人得说出来吧
System's broken. Somebody had to call it out.
而且我认为一场新闻发布会
And here I thought a press conference
是发布消息
was for dispensing information,
而调动大家的情绪 是我理解错了
not calling people out. My mistake.
我最后听到的 你承认了一项犯罪
Well, last I heard, you commit a crime,
你得承担后果 就是这样
you suffer the consequences, end of story.
你知道有多少次你和杰米来找我
You know how many times you and Jamie have come to me
要搜查令或者是一张传票
for a search warrant or a subpoena,
并且你们没什么证据就能拿到
and you haven't had everything to get it?
对 但很多次都没有
Yeah, about as many times
你说不行
as you've said no.
打断一下 我没明白
I'm sorry, I still don't understand.
如果你知道谁烧了我们的家
If you know who burned our house down,
那他为什么还没被抓
then why is he still walking?
这叫做司法反常
It's something called judicial perversion.
司法转移
Judicial diversion.
是一项政策
It's a policy
对那些非暴力犯罪减少保释金
where nonviolent offenders get reduced bail
和康复 社区服务代替呆在牢里
and rehab, community service instead of jail time.
这叫做溺爱犯罪
It's called mollycoddling criminals.
- 没错 - 你们有什么事情
- Exactly. - Is there anything
是怪不到地检头上的
that you guys don't blame on the attorneys?
我恐怕现在
Well, I'm afraid at the moment,
有太多的事情要怪了
there happens to be plenty to blame.
上帝保佑
Amen to that.
拥有自由主义的地检和市长
That's what you get for having
就是这个下场
a liberal D.A. And a liberal mayor.
好像警察就没犯过错
Like cops don't make mistakes?
没人这么说
Nobody's saying that.
平心而论 我能理解他为什么只用付少额的保释金
To be fair, I understand why he got a reduced bail.
他没有因为重罪被捕
His arrest wasn't for a large felony weight.
那他和违法黑帮的关系怎么说
Well, how about his affiliation with an illegal gang?
或者是他的犯罪记录
Or his criminal record?
他在墨西哥的犯罪记录
His criminal record in Mexico
背景审查的时候没有去查
doesn't come up in a background check.
如果你在国际刑警组织里查一下不就好了
It would if you ran him through Interpol.
我为什么要到国际刑警组织里
Why would I run a low-level drug dealer
去调查一个低级毒贩子
through Interpol?
你为什么不呢
Why wouldn't you?
我第一次来参与家庭聚餐的时候
You know, when I first started coming to these family dinners
你们大伙一直在争论不休 我非常紧张
and you guys would argue, I would get really nervous
因为我怕你们之间不会再说话了
'cause I thought maybe you'd never talk to each other again.
但..
But...
你们还是这样
you do.
不停地讲
You just keep talking.
无论发生了什么
Come hell or high water.
你是说我们讲太多了吗
You saying we talk too much?
不是
No.
别担心 埃迪
Well, don't worry, Eddie.
不管你做什么 你在这餐桌上仍然金光闪耀
No matter what you do, you're golden at this table.
是吗
I am?
只要你还穿着警服
As long as you wear NYPD blue.
我不知道你要来
I didn't know you were coming here.
小迪没和我说过
Edit never called me.
我没告诉她
I didn't tell her.
我能进来吗
May I come in?
我打赌她肯定生我气了
I bet she's mad at me.
那是肯定的
Well, why wouldn't she be?
她告诉你一些好消息
She came to give you some good news,
你却泼她冷水
and you rained on her parade.
好消息应该是她嫁给了
The good news would've been she's marrying someone
一位能负担的起她以前生活的男人
who could afford to give her the life that she's used to.
那是什么样的生活
And what life would that be?
你丈夫因诈骗入狱
One where your husband's in prison for fraud
她想把你踢出她的生活这种生活吗
and she wants to cut you out of her life?
她应该心存感激
She should be grateful.
我们给了她所有
We gave her everything.
你丈夫骗光了别人的积蓄
Your husband cheated people out of their savings.
你侮辱了她带回来的每一个人
You insulted every guy she ever brought around.
我实话实说
I tell the truth.
真相就是我赚不够钱吗
And the truth about me is I don't make
我信错宗教了吗
enough money? I'm the wrong religion?
我没住在富人区吗
I live in the wrong borough?
我不会道歉
I won't apologize
我这是为了我女儿好
for wanting what's best for my daughter.
- 我是你女儿最好的归宿 - 哦 因为你爱她吗
- I'm what's best for your daughter. - Oh, because you love her?
爱能用来付账单吗
And that's gonna take care of the bills?
我过得很舒适 我的家人也会这样子
I live a comfortable life, and my family will, too.
是否能满足你的标准 我不知道
Will it meet your standards? I don't know.
但我的家人永远是第一位
But my family will always come first.
这些心灵鸡汤在明信片里说说就好了
That sounds great on a Hallmark card.
现实呢
But in reality?
大不一样
Not so much.
我不想要小迪最后...
I don't want Edit to end up...
像你一样吗
Like you did?
可能你需要换个角度
Maybe you need to see the world
看一下这个世界
through a different set of glasses.
我的确不相信你那一套乐观天真的想法
Well, I certainly don't trust the rose-colored ones you wear.
你还没试过呢
You haven't tried them on yet.
我正在开庭审前听证会呢 爷爷
I'm in the middle of pretrial hearings, Pop.
你把我叫到这来
You call me out here for this.
我给你做了你最爱的三明治
I made you your favorite sandwich.
谢谢你 我们在这儿干嘛
Thank you. Now, what are we doing out here?
让你从地检署出来
Getting you out of the office.
地检署没有问题 老爸才是
My office is not the problem. Dad is.
是他吗 为什么
Oh, is he, now? Why?
因为他说出了他的感受
'Cause he says what he feels?
在无数的观众面前
In front of millions of viewers
在我作为局长的第一场新闻发布会上
at my first press conference as bureau chief?
他本可以温和一点
Yeah, he could've tempered it down.
你是指和稀泥吗
You mean watered it down?
随你怎么叫
Whatever you want to call it.
你生气是因为
You're upset because
他的语气是警察局长
he talked like the police commissioner
而不是你父亲
and not your father.
我觉得他也没有第二条路可以走了
I don't see how he could've handled it any other way.
你当然可以站在他角度说话
Of course you're gonna take his side.
我没有站边
I'm not taking sides.
你为什么把这事这么私人化
Why are you taking this so personally?
我能扛得住来自其他检察官
I can take the slings and arrows from other attorneys
地检 甚至是媒体的灾难 但...
and the D.A. And even the press, but...
但是不能是你父亲
But not your father?
他在批评地检署
He was criticizing
不是你
the D.A.'s office, not you.
并不是那样子
That's not what it felt like,
是我坐在那里 承受众人的目光
and I was the one up there taking the heat.
你在工作和家庭中感到困惑
You're confusing work and family.
你父亲
Your father
有权力不同意地检
has the right to disagree with the D.A.--
没错 在公共场合
yes, in public,
也没错 甚至你就站在他的旁边
and yes, even with you standing there next to him--
因为这是他的职责
because it's his job.
但无论发生什么
But no matter what happens,
你总是能够得到他的爱和支持
you'll always have his love and support.
你每次离开家 就得先汇报
Every time you leave the house, you have to call first
你去哪里
to say where you're going.
如果回来晚了
If you're gonna be late getting back
或者火车晚点了
or your train is delayed,
车子抛锚了 也得汇报
your car breaks down, you need to call us
要非常详细
with the details.
那我应该告诉你们可卡因和芬太尼的交易
Then I should tell you the coke and fentanyl exchange
可能今晚进行
may be going down tonight.
- "可能今晚进行" - 我今天下午
- "May be going down tonight"? - I'll get a call
会收到确认线报
this afternoon to confirm.
哪里
Where?
老旧的糖果工厂
The old candy factory.
我不知道有多少人
I don't know how many people.
一般有6 7个吧 有双特雷黑帮的成员
Usually six or seven total. Members of the Double Treys,
曼诺·圣戈亚托的成员 还有我
Mano Sangriento, me.
真棒 我们现在知道在哪里交易了
Good. Now we know where it's going down.
没必要让他上场了
So we don't need him to do this.
罗哈斯期望我能够到场处理这次交易
Rojas expects me to be there to handle the money.
如果他发现我不在 他就会逃之夭夭了
If he finds out I'm not, he'll be in the wind.
别相信他
Don't trust him.
收起你脸上的贱笑
Wipe that smile off your face.
很难收起来 因为你是真的有意思
That's hard to do 'cause you're so damn entertaining.
- 丹尼 丹尼 - 雷根 雷根
- Danny. Danny. - Reagan! Reagan!
出去
Outside.
现在
Now!
这对你来说太私人化了
This is too personal for you
- 你没法处理这... - 这不是个人恩怨
- and you cannot handle this... - It's not personal.
我不相信这狗娘养的 好吗
I don't trust the son of a bitch, okay?
我们正在努力
Well, we're on it.
- 你不了解那家伙的套路 - 不吗
- You don't know how that guy works. - No?
35年前 我父亲越过国境
35 years ago, my father crossed the border
逃离曼诺·圣戈亚托
to get away from Mano Sangriento.
他最后赚够了钱
Okay, when he finally had enough money,
回去把他剩下的家人接回来
he went back to get the rest of his family.
圣戈亚托已经杀光了他们家的每一个人
Sangriento had killed every last one of them.
所以...
So...
别和我说 我不了解他
don't tell me I don't know him.
好吧 我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry.
真的
I am.
但你这是在铤而走险 相信这个人
But you're playing with fire, trusting this guy.
你才在铤而走险
You're the one playing with fire,
让他那样子和你见面
letting him get to you like that.
你要么遵守我的规则
You either play by my rules,
要么就离开这个团队
or you get the hell off my team.
好的 我们看到德尔加多了
Okay. We got Delgado.
朋友
Amigo.
不错 老兄
我只卖最好的货
你带现金了吗
你要数数吗
我知道你住哪里
I know where you live.
听我信号 准备冲
On my signal, we're gonna go.
一
One.
二
Two.
等等 他要去哪里
Wait a minute. Where the hell is he going?
我不知道 他车在前面啊
I don't know. His car's in the front.
他要干嘛
What the hell is he doing?
- 三 - 别 等等
- Three. - No. Wait.
- 别 等等 - 冲冲冲
- No, wait! No! - Go, go, go.
冲 冲
Move, move!
嘿 这是个圈套 等等
Hey. It's a setup. Hold on!
嘿
Hey!
救命 救我 救我
Help! Help me! Help me!
来这儿 来这
Come here, come here.
撑住
Hang on!
贝兹 胡椒粉
Baez, it's pepper spray!
胡椒粉
It's pepper spray!
德尔加多
Delgado?!
Delgado?
啊
Aah!
这是迪吉里杜管
It's a didgeridoo.
一种澳大利亚的管乐器 有点像喇叭
An Australian wind instrument, a little bit like a trumpet.
哦
Oh.
谢谢你
Thank you.
是澳大利亚首相的礼物
It's a gift from the prime minister of Australia
感谢上周招待他
for hosting him last week.
给纽约警局博物馆的馈赠吗
A donation to the NYPD Museum?
布莱恩情况有所好转
Brian's doing better.
没错 谢谢你
He is, thank you.
估计这几周你都不会来了吧
Thought you weren't coming in for a few weeks.
我和杰米说 放他几小时的假
I told Jimmy I'd relieve him for a few hours.
我能用休息时间
I could use the break.
如果用休息时间上班 事情就不那么好了
Things are bad if work's a break.
实际上 事情非常好
Actually, things are very good.
布莱恩能自主呼吸了
Brian is breathing on his own,
他一直在抱怨医院的伙食
he's complaining about hospital food,
他们明天就让他出院
and they're gonna release him tomorrow.
不错
Good news.
或许你可以
Well, maybe you should
重新考虑无笑脸政策了
rethink that no-smile policy.
我陪你一起去医院探访过很多警官
I have accompanied you on many, many hospital visits
他们有些在执勤时受伤
to officers who have been injured in the line of duty,
有些在执勤时殉难
some who have died in the line of duty.
我知道这是你的工作
I knew it was your job.
我一直没能完全理解的是拜访警官家人
What I never fully understood was just how important
是多么重要的事情
your visit is to the officer's family.
现在我知道了
And now I know.
谢谢你
Thank you.
狗日的 他给我们下套 我告诉过你别相信他
Son of a bitch, he set us up. I told you not to trust him.
我们还不知道
We don't know that yet.
这还不明显嘛
Of course he set us up.
他在箱子爆炸前就逃了
He got the hell out of there right before the boxes exploded.
- 他怎么知道的 - 他知道接下来的事情
- How the hell would he know?! - He knew what was coming.
那他为什么回到了公寓
Then why did he go back to his apartment?
什么
What?
你看脚踝监视器
Look at the ankle monitor.
这上面显示他在那里
It proves that he's there.
那 到底怎么回事
Then, what happened?
- 我和他见了面之后我就告诉你们 - 别 别
- Well, I'll let you know after I see him. - No, no, no, no.
我们见了他之后你告诉他们
You'll let 'em know after we see him.
我们和你去
We're going with you.
走吧
Let's go.
德尔加多 警察
Delgado? Police!
我以为GPS上显示他在这里
I thought the GPS said he was here.
没错啊
It did.
是我莫利纳探员 路易斯
It's Agent Molina, Luis.
我们需要谈谈
We need to talk to you.
路易斯
Luis?
请进
Please, come in.
我很高兴你能来
You know, I'm glad you came.
有件事情我一直想告诉你
Something I've been wanting to tell you.
什么事情
What's that?
你清楚你妻子的直升机事故吗
You know your wife's helicopter accident?
实际上不是一起意外事故
It really wasn't an accident.
全是由曼诺·圣戈亚托策划的
It was all arranged by Mano Sangriento,
因为你先和他们开战的
because you started playing games with them.
你个狗日的 你他妈人在哪里
You son of a bitch. Where the hell are you?
在哪儿
Where are you?!
你真的不应该和他们开战
You really shouldn't play games with them.
你知道为什么吗
And do you know why?
我不在乎原因
I don't give a damn why.
因为他们永远是赢家
Because they always win.
你在哪里 德尔加多
Where are you, Delgado?
你可真是位硬汉啊
Real tough guy, huh?
不能和我面对面吗
Couldn't come face me?
我这不和你面对面吗 警探
Oh, I am facing you, Detective.
你知道我看到了什么吗 失败者
And you know what I see? A loser.
如果你不介意 我要去喝杯小酒了
Now, if you'll excuse me, I'm gonna go mix myself a drink.
我让技术组来 追踪这段视频
I'll get TARU in here, run a trace on the video.
你告诉我GPS显示他在这里
You told me the GPS said he was here.
这狗娘养的不在这里
The son of a bitch isn't here!
GPS显示他之前在这里
It said that he was here.
漂亮
Good one.
怎么了
Hello?
嗨
Hey.
埃迪 老妈和我
Eddie, uh, Mom and I--
我们给你做了晚饭
we made dinner for you.
我老妈不下厨
- My mom doesn't cook. - What did I
我一直怎么和你说的 小迪
always tell you, Edit?
"忘记橱柜里的餐盘
"Forget the dishes on the shelf,
成为餐盘上的佳肴"
be a tasty dish yourself"?
所以我们从Balthazar点了外卖
So, we ordered takeout from Balthazar's.
喝点红酒吗
Want some wine?
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
好的
Okay.
她点了最贵的餐馆的外卖
She ordered from the most expensive restaurant,
我们要付钱啊
and we are gonna foot the bill.
- 我知道 - 你知道
- Yeah, I know. - You know?
你怎么想的
What were you thinking?
我觉得这能做出点补偿
I thought it would be good to make amends.
她带了家庭相册过来吗
She brought the family photo album?
我的主意
Well, that was my idea.
如果她喝点酒是不是会变得好一些
Does it get better if she has a few drinks?
如果我们喝点酒 才会变好
Well, it gets better if we do.
小迪 你第一次穿比基尼
Edit, your first bikini!
很高兴那之后你胸部还能变大
It's a good thing you grew some boobs after that.
和你一起的那家伙叫什么来着
Who was that guy that you went with?
他叫什么啊
What was his name?
哦 斯坦
Oh. Stan.
斯坦 没错
Stan. That's right.
他老爸是一名心脏病医生
His father was a cardiologist.
- 他怎么了 - 额
- What ever happened to him? - Well,
老妈 斯坦也当了心脏病医生
Mom, uh, Stan became a cardiologist, too,
他住在博卡区
and he lives in Boca.
- 嗯 - 多棒的孩子
- Ah. - Oh. Nice boy.
- 帮我倒满 - 嗯
- I'll have a refill. - Yeah.
老妈 你把我每个带回家的男孩子都吓跑了
Mom, you scared off every boy I ever brought home.
如果他们都被吓跑了 那他们一个都不值得拥有你
If they were all scared off, then none of them deserve you.
那就是你的借口吗
Is that your excuse?
我说真的
It's true.
他们都跑了 除了一个人
They all ran, except for one.
他是唯一一个跑回来的
He's the only one who came back.
我爱你
I love you.
出什么事了吗
Something wrong?
没
No.
你得来看看这个 杰米
You've got to see this, Jamie.
埃迪在万圣节
Eddie dressed as Jessica Rabbit
把自己打扮成杰西卡兔
for Halloween.
哦 其实我穿那身还蛮性感的
Ooh, I actually look pretty hot in that one.
- 那我们还等什么 - 嗯
- Well, what are we waiting for? - Mm.
你已经把鱼饵装上了吗
You already put the bait on?
- 我想帮你省些麻烦 - 红蚯蚓吗
- Thought I'd save you the trouble. - It's a blood worm?
沙蚯蚓
Sand worms.
我本来想钓鲱鱼
I would have gone with herring.
你要我把底饵装上吗
You want me to put on a bottom bait?
别 我没叫你出来给我当男仆
No, I didn't ask you to come out here to valet the tackle.
好吧
Okay.
你知道我教你钓鱼的时候你多大吗
You know how old you were when I taught you to fish?
- 不记得了 - 七岁
- No. - Seven.
实际上 我完全没想教你钓鱼
Actually, I wasn't gonna teach you at all,
虽然我已经教过男孩了
even though I taught the boys.
因为我是女孩吗
Because I was a girl?
不是
No.
因为这种活动
Because it is the kind of activity
即使你做得再完美
where even if you do everything perfectly,
也没法保证有鱼上钩
there's no guarantee of a fish.
如果我没听错的话 还有什么像这样子的事情吗
And what else is like that, if I'm hearing you correctly?
当上司
Being a boss.
一个错误 闪光灯就一个劲的冲了过来
One slipup, and the searchlight comes on hot and fast.
和我说说
Tell me about it.
爷爷说我把新闻发布会看的太私人了
Pop told me I took the press conference personally.
说我希望你能表现得更像一位爱护孩子的父亲
That I was expecting you'd act more like
而不是警察局长
a protective father than the PC.
你觉得呢
And what do you think?
我的错误就是自己表现得像尊敬长辈的女儿
That my mistake was acting like a respectful daughter,
让你把话都说完了
letting you have the last word.
下次呢
And the next time?
我还是一如既往的尊敬你
I will always be respectful of you.
没有其它方式 但是...
Couldn't be any other way, but...
我也需要尊敬我的办公室
I need to respect my office, too.
或许 还是尽可能少的开联合新闻发布会吧
And maybe keep the joint press conferences to a minimum.
没错 这样子好
Yeah. That, too.
喔
Ooh.
如你所知
Well, what do you know.
结果
Results.